CanYouSeeMe.org
===============

Our Privacy Policy
------------------

The privacy of the visitors to Canyouseeme.org is important to us.

At Canyouseeme.org, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit canyouseeme.org, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

We are the Data Controller of your information.

Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Information we collect and the specific context in which we collect the information:

* Canyouseeme.org needs to perform a service (port check) with you
* You have given Canyouseeme.org permission to do so
* Processing your personal information is in Canyouseeme.org legitimate interests
* Canyouseeme.org needs to comply with the law

Canyouseeme.org will retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.
* The right of rectification.
* The right to object.
* The right of restriction.
* The right to data portability
* The right to withdraw consent

### Log Files

Canyouseeme.org follows a standard procedure of using log files. The information collected by log files include -

* IP(Internet Protocol) Address
* Web Browser type
* Date and time stamp
* Referring/exit pages

These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site and gathering demographic information.

### Site Statistics

Our site uses Google Analytics which is a website analytics service provided by Google Inc. When you use this website, the cookie will collect data about your use of the website, and then transmitted to Google servers of American. Google doesn't publish your IP address on any activities by Google. If you use this website, you tolerate Google collecting your personal information to do all of the above mentioned.

### Cookies & Web Beacons

Like any other website, canyouseeme.org uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitor's preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the user's experience by customizing our web page content based on visitor's browser type and/or other information.

* Google Analytics - For Analytics
* Twitter, Facebook, Google Plus, YouTube - For social interaction

### Google DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL: https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads

You could opt out of personalized ads and control how google show you ads by visiting this page : [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/) and [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

### Our Advertising Partners

Some advertisers (listed on our ads.txt ) on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Some of our major advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.

* Google - [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)

Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on canyouseeme.org, which are sent directly to users' browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

You can choose to disable or turn off our cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings, However this may affect the usability of our website, and other websites as well.

### Children's Information

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity. Canyouseeme.org does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.

©2004-2020 • Canyouseeme.org • All Rights Reserved. [Privacy Policy](https://canyouseeme.org/privacy.php)

**LEGAL DISCLAIMER**  
THE INFORMATION ON THIS PAGE IS STRICTLY FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO OBEY ALL APPLICABLE LOCAL, STATE AND FEDERAL LAWS. WE ASSUME NO LIABILITY AND ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY MISUSE OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY THE USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THIS PAGE.
